

Bio/Profile

A solution-oriented senior full stack developer, product manager and cloud architect with a wide variety of professional skills and experience. Has nearly two decades of software developer experience with a keen eye for UI/UX Design.

Passionate about transforming companies through the use of technology and the cloud.

Education/Certificates

UI/UX Design ASP.NET Core Microsoft ADO.NET Microsoft Visual C# .NET SQL Database Management PHP Web Development -Humber College (2004-2005)

Social Media

Twitter

twitter.com/dwainbrowne

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/dwainbrowne

Contact Me



+1 416-799 2458



dwain@snapsuite.io



102-2300 Upper Middle Rd W Oakville, ON L6M 0T4

Dwain Browne

www.dwain.me | linkedin.com/in/dwainbrowne

Cloud Architect | Product Manager | Full Stack Developer

Relevant Experience

Product Manager/Owner

- Spearheaded the development and design of new SaaS applications
- Advised upper management on technology, marketing, and design requirements
- Extensive testing and requirements gathering for web applications
- Authored whitepapers addressing the need for business cloud transformation

Developer & Cloud Solutions Architect

- Developed micro-service architecture applications for clients using .NET Core technologies
- Planned and implemented DevOps pipeline for continuous delivery, utilizing Git & Azure Dev Ops
- Designed, Implemented and Integrated Azure/AWS cloud technologies with on-premises solution
- Analyzed business processes and recommended improvements for increasing efficiency
 Provided technical support to cross-functional teams

Skills

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CLOUD ARCHITECT

C# .NET / CORE

UI / UX DESIGN

VUE JS/JAVASCRIPT

SQL/DB ADMIN

ADOBE SUITE

HTML5/CSS3/JS

VISUAL STUDIO

Technologies

Azure/AWS Cloud, CQRS Design Systems, Microsoft Technologies, SQL, Business Intelligence, SharePoint, Teams & Office 365 Development Platform

Soft Skills

Ridiculously Hard Worker

Critical Thinking

Public Speaking

Life Long Learner

Verbal and Written Communication

Driven

Experience

Software Consultant/Partner at SnapSuite Inc

Feb 2017 - Present

Developed and implemented new technology solutions for managing companies with revenue from \$5-30million. Ensure frictionless customer onboarding and integrate technology solutions with ongoing marketing campaigns.

CTO/Owner at Candev Services

2009 - Feb 2017

Managed a team of ten including five developers; coordinating CMS project development, product promotions, and marketing with strategic partners. Directly involved with sales and business development.

Other Companies

- Silverback Media Software Developer 2008-2009
- Advance Knowledge Network Software Developer 2004-2007
- First Yellow Web Developer 1999-2004